

## **CONTACT**

**PHONE:** 085738601017

EMAIL: dimasrifalta@gmail.com

WEB: Https://dimasrifalta.vercel.app

**HOME:** Cilandak Jakarta Selatan DKI

Jakarta - 12450

# **SKILLS**

PROGRAMING LANGUAGE: C#, PHP, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT, CSS

DATABASE: SQL Server, MYSQL and

Google Firebase

**FRONT-END:** 

React.js, Angular, JQuery

**BACK-END:** 

REST API, ASP.NET CORE, ASP.NET.MVC, CODEIGNITER

## **HOBBY**

Playing football, Hiking, Watch Movie

# **DIMAS RIFALTA**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

IT Professional with 2+ years of experience in developing web, batch, and business intelligence solutions for diverse industry clients. Highly instrumental in all phases of the SDLC, with expertise in algorithms and data structures. Successful in developing bespoke solutions, optimizing business procedures, processes, and productivity.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

2020 - Present

PT. Primalogic Inter Asia/Jakarta Selatan

- Develop and maintain accounting application, pension fund application, assurance application data-centric web applications and services using ASP.NET, C#.NET, LINQ, MS SQL, and Agile/SCRUM methodologies.
- Create and apply UI requirements utilizing Anggural 6 And React.js.
- Collaborate with business analysts, users, and federal agencies to collect requirements and provide implementation.
- Create automate deploy system to maintenance the new feature and bug fixing.

#### FREELANCE WEB DEVELOVER

2019-2021

FIVER / Web Freelance

- Create travel and touring applications based on customer requirements
- Assisted clients with diagnosis of software and hardware issues and concerns.
- Encouraged timely and relevant upgrades for clients' products as necessary.

### **EDUCATION**

**DIPLOMA 3** in Informatics Engineering *Politeknik Pos Indonesia* 

2017 - 2020